Terrifying Pompadour of Hell
Quiet Beast
Nice to meet you!
Wise Prince
Twin Crimson Blades
The Fruit of Evolution 2:
Before I Knew It, My Life Had It Made
Seiichi vs. Class F
Twin Fang Thrust
For real?!
With spirit
I'll send you packing!!
Smelly
Creep
Fatty
Idiot
Skill: "Events Led Me to Teaching
Failures in Another World.
But if a Teacher Doesn't Believe in Their Students,
Then What Are Teachers For?
I'm Sure They'll Be Able to
Use Magic if I Confront Them Physically!
Or So I Thought, Before Some Mysterious Power Really Let Them Activate Magic"
Want to do it?!
The water thing~
Ma
gi
c
Want to do it?!
The water thing~
Déjà vu
I leave it to you!
Fire
LOL
Thank You
Uwaaaaaaaah
Baird Lutra
Nice to meet you!
Fire?
Class Dismissed
Next Time
Reunited With Kannazuki Karen